<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Charlotte Stormwater</title>
    <link>https://charlottestormwater.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Charlotte Stormwater</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://charlottestormwater.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://charlottestormwater.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://charlottestormwater.com/about/</guid>
      <description>CharlotteStormwater.com is your go-to hub for staying informed and taking proactive steps to address stormwater challenges. Together, let&amp;rsquo;s build a resilient community that values sustainable stormwater practices for the benefit of current and future generations.&#xA;Best Management Practice (BMP) | Stormwater Control Measure (SCM) | Fatty Oils &amp;amp; Grease (FOG)&#xA;Oil Water Separator (OWS) | Private Septic Systems | Lift Station Maintenance (LS)&#xA;Need Help with a Notice of Maintenance Required (NMR) ?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://charlottestormwater.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://charlottestormwater.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Need Help with a Notice of Maintenance Required (NMR) ?&#xA;Fill out the contact form and someone from our team will be in touch shortly!&#xA;Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://charlottestormwater.com/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://charlottestormwater.com/links/</guid>
      <description>Charlotte Stormwater offers annual stormwater inspection reports, notice of violations (NOV) letters and notice of maintenance required (NMR) assistance. Does your property need help? Our team of local inspectors can help today.&#xA;https://www.charlottenc.gov/Services/Stormwater&#xA;Charlotte-Meckleburg Storm Water Services is a collaborative municipal and county stormwater utility, encompassing the City of Charlotte and the neighboring towns of Cornelius, Davidson, Huntersville, Matthews, Mint Hill, Pineville, and Mecklenburg County.&#xA;https://regionalstormwater.org/&#xA;Regional Stormwater Partnership of the Carolinas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulations</title>
      <link>https://charlottestormwater.com/regulations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://charlottestormwater.com/regulations/</guid>
      <description>Empowered by the NC State legislature, Charlotte-Meckleburg Stormwater Services has been granted the authority to formulate and implement ordinances that address specific community needs while adhering to federal and state stipulations. This collaborative approach enables responsive governance, allowing communities to tailor their regulations in alignment with local requirements and overarching legislative mandates.&#xA;Did you recieve a Notice of Violation or Notice of Maintenance Required? We can help!&#xA;Post-Construction Stormwater Control Ordinance (PCSO) Charlotte Metro, North Carolina Sec.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
